[
    {
      "question": "Ich habe _____.",
      "answer": "Fernweh",
      "options": ["Weltschmerz", "Fernweh", "Torschlusspanik", "Schadenfreude"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Er fühlt _______.",
      "answer": "Weltschmerz",
      "options": ["Fremdschämen", "Weltschmerz", "Lebensmüde", "Kopfkino"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Sie zeigt ________.",
      "answer": "Schadenfreude",
      "options": ["Torschlusspanik", "Kopfkino", "Fernweh", "Schadenfreude"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Ich hatte sofort ______.",
      "answer": "Kopfkino",
      "options": ["Lebensmüde", "Fremdschämen", "Kopfkino", "Weltschmerz"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Ich musste ________.",
      "answer": "Fremdschämen",
      "options": ["Fremdschämen", "verrückt", "Schadenfreude", "Fernweh"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Sie hat ________.",
      "answer": "Torschlusspanik",
      "options": ["Torschlusspanik", "Weltschmerz", "Fernweh", "Lebensmüde"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Bist du ______?",
      "answer": "lebensmüde",
      "options": ["verrückt", "lebensmüde", "mutig", "fremdschämen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Ich genieße die _______.",
      "answer": "Zweisamkeit",
      "options": ["Weltschmerz", "Torschlusspanik", "Zweisamkeit", "Kopfkino"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Ich habe meinen ______ besiegt.",
      "answer": "Schweinehund",
      "options": ["Lebensmüde", "Schweinehund", "Kopfkino", "Schadenfreude"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Er hat es ________.",
      "answer": "Verschlimmbessern",
      "options": ["Torschlusspanik", "Fremdschämen", "Verschlimmbessern", "Weltschmerz"]
    }
  ]
  